我在本次讲座中多次使用过运动学这个术语，但事实并非如此
I've used the term kinematics a number of times in this lecture and I haven't really
非常明确这意味着什么。运动学是研究数学的数学分支
been very clear about what it means. Kinematics is a branch of mathematics that studies the
身体或身体系统的运动。运动学关注事物的位置
motion of a body or a system of bodies. Kinematics is concerned with the positions of things
或者事物之间的角度与速度有关。这些可以是转化的
or the angles between things and is concerned with velocities. These can be translational
速度或它们可以是角速度。
velocities or they could be angular velocities.
运动学不关心力和力矩。这是动态的业务。
Kinematics is not concerned with forces and moments. That's the business of dynamics.
因此，在运动学中，人们研究机制，例如此处所示的机制并尝试理解
So in kinematics people study mechanisms such as the ones shown here and try to understand
一个身体的运动如何与另一个身体的运动相关。
how the motion of one body is related to the motion of another body.
我在这里展示了许多相当复杂的机制的例子。在运动学中，是
I have shown here examples of a number of quite complex mechanisms. In kinematics, is
研究这些机制的各个组成部分的运动。在机器人技术中，我们考虑
the study of the motion of the various components of these mechanisms. In robotics, we consider
两个运动学问题。
two kinematic problems.
首先，我们在这个特定的讲座中讨论的是所谓的前向运动学
First one, in what we discuss in this particular lecture is what's called the forward kinematic
问题。这是机器人关节角度，机器人工具尖端的姿势是什么？
problem. And that is given the robot joint angles, what's the pose of the robot's tool tip?
第二个问题称为反向运动学。我们将在下一个讨论这个问题
The second problem is called the inverse kinematics. And we're going to discuss that in the next
演讲。鉴于我知道我想要机器人在叛逃者身上的姿势，问题
lecture. Given that I know the pose that I want the robot in-defector to have, the problem
是为了确定实现这一目标所需的关节角度。让我来
is to determine what are the joint angles required in order to achieve that. Let me
留下你真正喜欢的这句话。这是关于运动学的。
leave you with this quote I really like. It's about kinematics.